fcbankingonline.com 2019-04-24

# FACTS

                                                                                               Rev. August 2014
                   WHAT DOES FIRST COMMONWEALTH FINANCIAL CORPORATION
   FACTS           DO WITH YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?
Why?               Financial companies choose how they share your personal information. Federal law gives
                   consumers the right to limit some but not all sharing. Federal law also requires us to tell you how
                   we collect, share, and protect your personal information. Please read this notice carefully to
                   understand what we do.
What?              The types of personal information we collect and share depend on the product or service you
                   have with us. This information can include:
                     Social Security Number and income
                     account balances and payment history
                     credit history and account transactions
How?               All financial companies need to share customers’ personal information to run their everyday
                   business. In the section below, we list the reasons financial companies can share their
                   customers’ personal information; the reasons First Commonwealth Financial Corporation
                   chooses to share; and whether you can limit this sharing.
                                                                            Does
Reasons we can share your personal                                First Commonwealth                Can you limit
information                                                       Financial Corporation             this sharing?
                                                                           share?
For our everyday business purposes –
such as to process your transactions, maintain your
account(s), respond to court orders and legal                                Yes                           No
investigations, or report to credit bureaus
For our marketing purposes –
 to offer our products and services to you                                   Yes                           No
For joint marketing with other financial companies                           Yes                           No
For our affiliates’ everyday business purposes –
information about your transactions and experiences                          Yes                           No
For our affiliates’ everyday business purposes –
information about your creditworthiness                                      Yes                           Yes
For our affiliates to market to you                                          Yes                           Yes
For nonaffiliates to market to you                                           No                     We don’t share
To limit our         Call us toll free at 800.711.2265 and talk with our Engagement Center Representative.
sharing
                    Please note:
                    If you are a new customer, we can begin sharing your information 30 days from the date we sent
                    this notice. When you are no longer our customer, we continue to share your information as
                    described in this notice.
                    However, you can contact us at any time to limit our sharing.
Questions?         Call toll free 800.711.2265

Page 2
Who we are
Who is providing this notice?                 First Commonwealth Bank
                                              First Commonwealth Financial Corporation
                                              First Commonwealth Insurance Agency
What we do
How does First Commonwealth Financial    To protect your personal information from unauthorized access
Corporation protect my personal          and use, we use security measures that comply with federal law.
information?                             These measures include computer safeguards and secured files
                                         and buildings.
How does First Commonwealth Financial    We collect your personal information, for example, when you
Corporation collect my personal            open an account or deposit money
information?                               pay your bills or apply for a loan
                                           apply for insurance
                                         We also collect your personal information from others, such as
                                         credit bureaus, affiliates, or other companies.
Why can’t I limit all sharing?           Federal law gives you the right to limit only
                                           sharing for affiliates’ everyday business purposes –
                                              information about your creditworthiness
                                           affiliates from using your information to market to you
                                           sharing for nonaffiliates to market to you
                                          State laws and individual companies may give you additional
                                          rights to limit sharing.
What happens when I limit sharing for an Your choices will apply to everyone on your account – unless you
account I hold jointly with someone      tell us otherwise.
else?
Definitions
Affiliates                               Companies related by common ownership or control. They can
                                         be financial and nonfinancial companies.
                                           Our affiliates include financial companies such as First
                                              Commonwealth Bank, First Commonwealth Financial
                                              Corporation and First Commonwealth Insurance Agency.
Nonaffiliates                            Companies not related by common ownership or control. They
                                         can be financial and nonfinancial companies.
                                           First Commonwealth Financial Corporation does not share
                                              with nonaffiliates so they can market to you.
Joint marketing                          A formal agreement between nonaffiliated financial companies
                                         that together market financial products or services to you.
                                           Our joint marketing partners include credit card companies,
                                              insurance companies, and registered broker/dealer.
